Finding Aid for Valde Garcia Papers, 1999-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Other Records
  - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Press releases and newspaper columns
    - 1999-2000 (Box 13)
    - 2003-2005 (Box 13)
  - Public School Primer Education Funding (Garcia's presentation on school education funding (Box 13)
  - Twenty First Century Jobs Fund, Joint Select Committee on Oversight of 2005, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Valde Garcia Charter School, petition to charter (Box 13)
  - Photographs (Box 13)